They're listening.
The Silence is a horror, drama, thriller film directed by John R. Leonetti.
With the world under attack by deadly creatures who hunt by sound, a teen and her
family seek refuge outside the city and encounter a mysterious cult.
Hugh Andrews, played by Stanley Tucci.
Ally Andrews, played by Kiernan Shipka.
Kelly Andrews, played by Miranda Otto.
Lynn, played by Kate Trotter.
Glenn, played by John Corbett.
Jude Andrews, played by Kyle Breitkopf.
The Silence is a 2019 post-apocalyptic horror film directed by John R.
Leonetti and starring Kiernan Shipka, Stanley
Tucci, Miranda Otto, and John Corbett.
The screenplay by Carey and Shane Van Dyke adapts the 2015
horror novel of the same name by Tim Lebbon.
The film depicts a world under attack by creatures who hunt by sound.
Shipka plays a deaf teenager who seeks shelter with her family, and
a cult tries to take advantage of her fertility.
Netflix released The Silence on April 10, 2019.
It was also released in theaters in seven countries in
the rest of 2019, grossing $2.3 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, deaf,
post-apocalyptic future, survival, creature.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.